http://www.coppin.edu/terms

Coronavirus Preparedness & Updates
View the latest campus news & information surrounding COVID-19.
You are here:
Home
Terms and disclaimer
Terms and disclaimer
Coppin State University's position on privacy and our web privacy policy in context
Privacy Statement and Policy
We take data security and the privacy of your personal information very seriously. Maryland law mandates that State agencies shall not create personal records unless the need for the information is clearly established and that personal records shall be relevant to the purposes for which they are collected, be accurate and current, and not be obtained by fraudulent means. State officials who request personal data from citizens must notify the citizens regarding the purposes for which the information is collected; consequences to the citizen for refusing to provide the personal information; the citizen's right to inspect and correct personal records; whether the information is generally available for public inspection; and whether the information is made available to other entities. Coppin State University is committed to providing you with web sites over which you may securely and confidently transact business.
CSU collects limited data from users when accessing the main campus website and connected microsites. This data is utilized to monitor website traffic and usage, as well as ensure website security.
Additional voluntarily supplied data may be collected in web-based forms in support of events and educational services, or other legitimate business purposes of the university.
Data collected is not sold, transferred, or utilized by any third party, except as required by law enforcement.
